(Howard:)And now the
kung pao chicken.
(Leonard:)Ah, yeah.
Wow.
(Raj:)Smooth.
(Howard:)And finally,
(Howard:)my moo shu pork.
(Raj:)Whoo-hoo!
Oh, there you have
it, gentlemen.
(Howard:)Our entire dinner
unpacked by robot.
(Raj:)And it only took 28 minutes.
(Sheldon:)Impressive,
(Sheldon:)but we must be cautious.
Why?
(Sheldon:)Today, it's a Chinese food
retrieval robot.
(Sheldon:)Tomorrow,
it travels back in time
(Sheldon:)and tries to kill Sarah Connor.
(Leonard:)I don't think that's
going to happen, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)No one ever does.
(Sheldon:)That's why it happens.
(Penny(arriving):)Hey. Is the food here?
(Penny(arriving):)Ooh. What's that?
(Howard:)That, dear lady,
(Howard:)is the Wolowitz
Programmable Hand,
(Howard:)designed
for extravehicular repairs
(Howard:)on the International
Space Station.
(Penny:)Ah, cool.
(Howard:)Ask me to pass the soy sauce.
(Penny:)Oh, does that come up much
on the space station?